Neha Shakya

+977-9818885966 · neha211shakya@gmail.com Imadol, Lalitpur

SUMMARY

As a Bachelor of Computer Information System student. With experience in designing, communicator, and business development. I have developed strong analytical, problem-solving, communication, and time management skills. My background in this sector has allowed me to enhance my skills in team collaboration, communication, and presentation. These skills make me a strong candidate for the position of Project manager role at your company.

KEY COMPETENCIES

Time Management

Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop

Trello, Jira

Figma

Commmunication

Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop

Project managment Skills

Research and Analytic skills

Commmunication Multi-tasking skills Stagtegic thinking

EDUCATION

Apex College (Bachelor) 2019 - 2024

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Kali Infotech Pvt.Ltd (Ui/Ux Designer and Graphic Designer)

Aug 2022 - 2023 Feb

- Designed user-friendly interfaces for websites and mobile applications, improving user engagement.
- Created visually compelling branding materials, including logos, brochures, and social media post, aligning with client vision and market trends.
- Worked closely with clients to understand their needs and deliver designs that exceeded expectations.
- Utilized tools like Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign to produce high-quality visuals.

KUSH Fintech Consultant (Designer and Client-Communicator)

May 2023 - 2024 Jan

- · Managed multiple design projects simultaneously, ensuring quality and timely delivery.
- Utilized tools like Adobe Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign to produce high-quality visuals.
- Managed multiple concurrent projects using tools like Trello, ensuring deadlines and quality standards were met.
- Liaised with clients to understand their requirements thoroughly and effectively communicated these to the team, ensuring seamless project execution and client satisfaction.

Susankya global (Business Development)

Mar 2024- 2024 Jul

- Identified and targeted important audiences to help drive business development.
- Connect with a large number of individuals in the industry.
- Attend meetings with clients to understand their requirements and problems.
- Collaborated with teams to ensure seamless project execution and client satisfaction while adhering to the client's budget.

RELEVENT PORJECT

Minor II (E-Bidding System), Major Project (E- Commerce Application)

- · Designed project UI/UX and defined the project scope, objectives, and timeline for effective planning
- Planning and allocating the tasks based on the project timeline.
- Tracking the project milestones and ensuring the tasks are completely on time using Trello.
- Collaborating with the team using GitHub for version control, Ensuring smooth integration of code changes
- Gathering feedback from our supervisors to incorporate changes and improvements into the project.
- Comprehensive report writing form the project objectives, mission, vision, literature review, methodologies, testing, integration, summary, and conclusions.
- Preparation of all the diagrams to be included in the reports (DFD level 0,1,2, ERD, Use Case Diagram, Context Flow Diagram).
- Presentation of the project along with my team members for our project demo, pre-defense, and defense.